<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cutlass Bearing on 1972 Allied Chance 30-30</title>
    <link>http://alliedchance30.com/tags/cutlass-bearing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cutlass Bearing on 1972 Allied Chance 30-30</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://alliedchance30.com/tags/cutlass-bearing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Replacing the Engine Mounts</title>
      <link>http://alliedchance30.com/projects/2014/06/15/linked-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alliedchance30.com/projects/2014/06/15/linked-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Need new engine mounts what do you think ??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see these mounts are done and for the most part they are done because they were not installed correctly in the first place. The lock nuts are missing and this has caused excessive vibration and wear on the mounts. At this time we are replaceint the cutlass bearing and the propeller shaft (see other articles) and it is all conected so this of course got added the the task list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morbi varius ex vel justo dictum placerat. Sed ac arcu pretium, varius elit eget, gravida purus. Fusce sit amet massa mollis eros tincidunt sollicitudin. Suspendisse iaculis cursus mauris ut sagittis. Interdum et malesuada fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus. Maecenas elit ligula, molestie quis magna eu, semper posuere lorem. Mauris a justo pharetra, congue ex eget, tincidunt massa. Maecenas sit amet neque lorem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curabitur at elementum quam. Curabitur tristique elit non sapien aliquam vulputate. Vivamus in odio tincidunt, tempor sem quis, tincidunt lacus. Mauris pulvinar nunc sed tempus dictum. Nam vel arcu quis mi fermentum ullamcorper non ac lacus. Donec aliquet vitae ante at imperdiet. Aenean scelerisque venenatis urna, eget elementum risus convallis ac. Nullam gravida arcu lacus, non consectetur augue pretium non. Duis dignissim eros id urna pretium congue. Nullam eu magna in sem sollicitudin tempor. Pellentesque vel convallis ligula. Quisque semper, turpis a rhoncus efficitur, magna nibh iaculis elit, eget tempor dolor eros ut mi. Maecenas eu placerat lacus. Praesent congue pretium nulla, sed suscipit metus rutrum vel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>